A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office of Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006
Library of Virginia
- III. Legislative Files, 2002-2005 (accession 42414)., Extent: 47.95 cubic feet (137 boxes). (Box 38-174)
  - 2003 Session
    - House of Delegates
      - Session Statistics, Vetoed Bills, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Governor's Recommendations for Amendments, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Governor's Recommendations Adopted, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Bills Passed House and Senate, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Bill and Resolution Status Report, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - HB 1375 (03) Notice of Annexation (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - HB 1377 (03) Special License Plates; Repeal of Authorization for some Plates (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - HB 1381 (03) World War II Veterans Memorial Highway; WWII Veterans Memorial Bridge (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - HB 1382 (03) Courthouse and Courtroom Security; Assessment (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - HB 1383 (03) Central Criminal Records Exchange; Criminal Nonsupport (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - HB 1385 (03) Motorcycle Headlights, Tail Lights, Brake Lights, and License Plate Illumination (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - HB 1393 (03) Virginia Truth in Revenue Service Report Act (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - HB 1398 (03) Enhanced Enforcement of Litter Laws (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - HB 1399 (03) Blood Samples Taken from DUI Accused (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - HB 1400 (03) Budget Bill (part one) (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - HB 1400 (03) Budget Bill (part two) (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - HB 1400 (03) Budget Bill (Box 70)
      - HB 1402 (03) Parental Consent for Abortion (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - HB 1403 (03) Prohibiting Attempted Purchase of Tobacco Products by Minors (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - HB 1404 (03) School Board Salaries; Southampton County (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - HB 1406 (03) Special License Plates; Supporters of CHOOSE LIFE (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - HB 1411 (03) Vietnam War Memorial Dedication and Veterans' Recognition Week (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - HB 1413 (03) Department of Human Resource Management; Duties (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - HB 1419 (03) Department of Historic Resources; Disbursements for Confederate Cemeteries (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - HB 1422 (03) Elections; Assistants to and Employees of General Registrars; Officers (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - HB 1424 (03) Payment of Medical Fees in Certain Criminal Cases (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - HB 1425 (03) Civil Remedies; Suit for Bad Check (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - HB 1429 (03) Motorcycle Handlebars (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - HB 1430 (03) Determining Speed of Vehicle with Various Devices (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - HB 1431 (03) Unemployment Compensation; Social Security Benefit (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - HB 1434 (03) Sex Offender Registry (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - HB 1437 (03) New Ballots After Death, Withdrawal or Disqualification of Nominee (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - HB 1440 (03) Vehicle Registrations (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - HB 1441 (03) Health Regulatory Boards; Disciplinary Procedures; Report Requirements (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - HB 1443 (03) Sale or Transfer of Motor Vehicle Dealerships (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - HB 1444 (03) Abolishes the Reciprocity Board (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - HB 1447 (03) Secondary Highway System Construction Allocations (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - HB 1449 (03) Compensation and Expenses of Members of Collegial Bodies (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - HB 1450 (03) Health; Certificate of Birth Resulting in Stillbirth (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - HB 1451 (03) Staunton State Scenic River (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - HB 1454 (03) Embezzlement and Larceny the Same (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - HB 1457 (03) Regulation of Truck Traffic on Secondary Highways (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - HB 1458 (03) Wage Garnishments (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - HB 1459 (03) Erosion and Sediment Control; Requirements for Plan Approval (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - HB 1461 (03) Visually Impaired Motorists (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - HB 1464 (03) General Achievement Diploma (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1471 (03) Alexandria Port Commission (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1472 (03) Bristol Parking Authority; Repeal (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1473 (03) Martinsville Parking Authority (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1474 (03) Peninsula Civic Recreation Center Authority (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1475 (03) Richmond-Henrico Metropolitan Area Commission (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1477 (03) Medical Malpractice; Former Rate Review Board (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1478 (03) Space Radiation Effects Laboratory (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1479 (03) Pulaski and Wytheville Parking Authority; Repeal (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1480 (03) Secondary Warning Lights (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1481 (03) Waterfowl Sanctuaries and Blinds (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1487 (03) Arterial Network of Highways (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - HB 1488 (03) Federal Revenue Sharing Funds by Localities for Highway-Related Purposes (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - HB 1491 (03) Use of Rifles in King George County (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - HB 1492 (03) Special License Plates, Generally (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - HB 1493 (03) Standards of Quality; Appropriate Learning Environment (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - HB 1496 (03) Criminal Procedure; Offenses Committed on Boundary of Localities (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - HB 1498 (03) Character of Education; Virginia Statement of Values (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - HB 1501 (03) Definition of Antique and Curio Firearms (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - HB 1503 (03) High School Diplomas; Civics Education Seal (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - HB 1504 (03) Harvesting of Oysters from Private Oyster Beds (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - HB 1505 (03) Emergency Water Supply Permit (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - HB 1506 (03) Capitol Hostess (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - HB 1508 (03) Voter Petition Requirements for Candidates (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - HB 1509 (03) State Networking Users Advisory Board (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - HB 1510 (03) State Public Records Advisory Council (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - HB 1511 (03) Blue Ridge Economic Development Advisory Council (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - HB 1514 (03) Parental Placement Adoptions (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - HB 1516 (03) Control of Firearms by Local Ordinance (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - HB 1518 (03) School Board Policies; Equal Access (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - HB 1520 (03) Juvenile and Domestic Relations Court Expanded Jurisdiction (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - HB 1521 (03) Salvage Vehicles; Branded Titles (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - HB 1524 (03) Reporting Radioactive Materials (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - HB 1525 (03) Waterway "Pass-Through" Zones; Local Ordinances; Penalties (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - HB 1526 (03) Personal Watercraft; Local Ordinances; Penalty (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - HB 1527 (03) Juvenile DUI and Refusal (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - HB 1528 (03) Albert G. Horton, Jr. Memorial Veterans' Cemetery (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - HB 1532 (03) Landfill Siting (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - HB 1533 (03) Juvenile Court; Definition of Family and Household Member (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - HB 1535 (03) State Emergency Medical Services Advisory Board (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - HB 1536 (03) Bonds; Longwood College (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - HB 1541 (03) Partial Birth Infanticide (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - HB 1542 (03) Campaign Finance Disclosure; Account to Comply; Federal Requirements (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - HB 1545 (03) Release of Procurement Records; Public Private Transaction Act 1995 and Education and Finance Act 2003 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - HB 1546 (03) State and Local Conflict of Interest Act (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - HB 1553 (03) Bicycles (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - HB 1556 (03) Charter; Town of Orange (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - HB 1558 (03) Local Consumer Utility Tax (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - HB 1559 (03) Truancy Court (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - HB 1560 (03) Vehicle Towing, Recovery, and Storage Charges (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - HB 1563 (03) Capitol Police (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - HB 1564 (03) Lottery; Voluntary Assignment of Prizes or Pledges as Collateral (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - HB 1569 (03) Virginia Office for Protection and Advocacy (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - HB 1572 (03) Juvenile Criminal Information; Schools (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - HB 1575 (03) Review and Approval of Certain Information Technology Projects (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - HB 1576 (03) Fraudulent Tax Return; Penalty (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - HB 1577 (03) Motor Fuels Tax (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - HB 1586 (03) Basic Requirements for Political Campaign Advertisements (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - HB 1587 (03) Retention of Cancelled Voter Registration Records (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - HB 1589 (03) Absentee Ballot Applications and Procedures (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - HB 1590 (03) Notice of Times and Locations for Registration (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - HB 1593 (03) Driver's License Numbers (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - HB 1594 (03) Crimes; Peeping (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - HB 1597 (03) Workforce Transition Act; Eligibility for Transitional Benefits (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - HB 1598 (03) Confinement of Animals Exposed to Rabies (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - HB 1599 (03) Competency to Stand Trial (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - HB 1600 (03) Budget Bill; Money Diverted from Transportation Trust Fund (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - HB 1601 (03) Alcoholic Beverage Control; Wine/Beer Licenses; Outdoor Performing Arts Facility (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - HB 1615 (03) Mechanics' Liens; 120-day Affidavit (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - HB 1617 (03) Hazing (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - HB 1619 (03) Fraudulent Use of Birth Certificates (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - HB 1621 (03) Certificate of Public Need; Regulations Authorizing Proper Cancer Care Centers (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - HB 1622 (03) Virginia Retirement System; Disability Benefits (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - HB 1623 (03) Mineral Mining Safety (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - HB 1624 (03) Individual Income Tax; Subtraction for Military Death Gratuity Payments (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - HB 1625 (03) Virginia War Memorial Foundation; Membership; Removal (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - HB 1627 (03) Virginia Scenic River Board (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - HB 1628 (03) Southside Virginia Business and Education Commission (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - HB 1630 (03) Refund of Taxes Erroneously Collected or Paid (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - HB 1635 (03) Income Tax; Voluntary Contribution of Tax Refund, VA Federal Humane Society (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - HB 1641 (03) Commercial Vehicles Stopped on Certain Roadways or Shoulders (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - HB 1643 (03) Polling Places; Prohibited Area; Emergency Situations (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - HB 1644 (03) Federal Campaign and Political Committees (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - HB 1651 (03) FOIA; Record Exemption for Employment Discrimination Investigations (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - HB 1652 (03) ABC; Wine and Beer Shippers' Licenses (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - HB 1657 (03) Special License Plates (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - HB 1661 (03) Private Piers (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - HB 1663 (03) Nonresident Hunting Fees (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - HB 1664 (03) Payments to Volunteer Rescue Squads by Localities (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - HB 1665 (03) Charter; City of Newport News (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - HB 1671 (03) Virginia Envirothon Program (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - HB 1673 (03) Assessment of Substantially Completed Buildings (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - HB 1677 (03) Flashing of Headlights on Certain Vehicles (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - HB 1678 (03) Uniform Statewide Building Code; Inspection of Rental Property (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - HB 1679 (03) Meetings of the Planning Commission and Board of Zoning Appeals (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - HB 1680 (03) "Out-of-Service" Inspections (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - HB 1681 (03) Prepayment of Fines for Violations of Speed Limits (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - HB 1683 (03) Offense Against Two or More Statutes or Ordinances; Double Jeopardy (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - HB 1684 (03) Line of Duty Act; Definitions (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - HB 1685 (03) Medicaid; Preadmission Screening (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - HB 1686 (03) Governor; Disposition of Official Correspondence and other Records (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - HB 1693 (03) Campaign Finance Disclosure Act; Electronic Filing of Reports (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - HB 1694 (03) Line of Duty Act; Definitions (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - HB 1695 (03) Health; Local Health Partnership Authorities (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - HB 1697 (03) Certified Nursing Facility Education Initiative (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - HB 1700 (03) Health; Regulations for Restaurant and Retail Food Establishments (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - HB 1702 (03) Penalty for Driving While Intoxicated (DUI) (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - HB 1704 (03) Higher Education; Reports of Expenditures of State Funds (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - HB 1706 (03) Board of Medicine's Guidelines; Ethical Practice Performance/Surgery (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - HB 1709 (03) Virginia Public Procurement Act; Multiphase Contracts/Professional Service (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - HB 1714 (03) Comprehensive Services Act; Family Assessment/Planning Team Referral (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - HB 1716 (03) Student Social Security Numbers (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - HB 1717 (03) Virginia Retirement System; Credit for Service in Armed Forces (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - HB 1718 (03) Date and Time of Death (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - HB 1719 (03) Charter; City of Bristol (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - HB 1720 (03) Office of Comprehensive Services for At-Risk Youth and Families; Vendor Management (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - HB 1722 (03) Condominium Act (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - HB 1727 (03) Protection of Certain Records in the Possession of Building Officials (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - HB 1730 (03) Regulation of Parking (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - HB 1731 (03) Charter; Town of Damascus (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - HB 1733 (03) Speeding in Highway Work Zones (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - HB 1735 (03) Special License Plates (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - HB 1736 (03) Charter; Town of Dumfries (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - HB 1737 (03) Accident and Sickness Insurance; Coverage for Lymphedema (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - HB 1738 (03) Economic Development Authorities (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - HB 1739 (03) Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act; Exemptions (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - HB 1743 (03) Notification of Cancer Patients Reports to Statewide Cancer Registry (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - HB 1744 (03) Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act; SSN's (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - HB 1746 (03) Virginia Real Estate Cooperative Act; Taxation (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - HB 1747 (03) Certificate of Public Need; Authorization of Certain Amendment (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - HB 1748 (03) Virginia Water Facilities Revolving Fund; Brownfields Remediation (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - HB 1749 (03) Board for Contractors; Application Affidavits (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - HB 1750 (03) Property Tax Exemptions (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - HB 1751 (03) Payment of Wages and Salaries (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - HB 1752 (03) Local "Crime Stoppers" Programs (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - HB 1753 (03) Names of Business Entities (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - HB 1754 (03) Sales and Use Tax Exemptions; Omnibus Extension Bill (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - HB 1756 (03) Health; Emergency Services (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - HB 1757 (03) Remediation for Certain Students (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - HB 1761 (03) Dept. of Information Technology; Contracts-Personal Computers (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - HB 1764 (03) Health Professions; Donation of Services (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - HB 1765 (03) Deer Kill Permit (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - HB 1767 (03) Certain Duties of Commissioner of Revenue/Treasurer; Extensions (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - HB 1769 (03) Payday Loan Advertising (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - HB 1770 (03) Medical Malpractice Action Limitation; Private Emergency Medical Care Attendants or Practitioners (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - HB 1774 (03) Department of Veterans Services (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - HB 1775 (03) ABC; Grounds ABC May Suspend or Revoke License (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - HB 1776 (03) Unclaimed Property; State Treasurer's Records (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - HB 1777 (03) Medical Malpractice Joint Underwriting Association (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - HB 1778 (03) Uniform Commercial Code; General Provisions (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - HB 1782 (03) Probation and Parole Services; Powers; Duties of Director of the Department of Corrections (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - HB 1784 (03) Administration; Records on Gubernatorial Appointees (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - HB 1786 (03) Provisional Drivers' Licenses (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - HB 1787 (03) Forfeiture of Recognizance Bond (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - HB 1788 (03) Activities of Former Local Officers and Employees (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - HB 1790 (03) Timelines for Decisions and Appeals of Teacher Grievances (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - HB 1791 (03) Virginia Retirement System; Group Life Insurance Program (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - HB 1792 (03) Defaults on Certain Educational Loans; Health Care Professional License (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - HB 1793 (03) Veterans Care Center; Names After Certain Medal of Honor Recipients (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - HB 1805 (03) Compliance with Subdivision Ordinance (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - HB 1808 (03) Treasurer; City of Galax (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - HB 1814 (03) Health; Protection of Complainants (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - HB 1817 (03) Private Security Services (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - HB 1819 (03) Perfection of Lien by General Contractor; Recordation and Notice (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - HB 1820 (03) Information Concerning Health Professionals; Post of Home Addresses (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - HB 1821 (03) Replacement of Manufactured Housing (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - HB 1822 (03) Medicaid-Buy-In (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - HB 1823 (03) Prescriptions for Therapeutic Equivalent Drugs; Virginia Voluntary Formulary (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - HB 1824 (03) Health Professions; Pharmacy Technicians (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - HB 1825 (03) Health Professions; Pharmacy and the Schedule of Drugs (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - HB 1826 (03) Health Insurance; Re-underwriting Individuals (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - HB 1827 (03) Virginia Securities Act (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - HB 1828 (03) Nonstock Corporations; Articles of Dissolution (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - HB 1829 (03) Business Entities; Articles of Merger (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - HB 1830 (03) Corporations and Limited Liability Companies; Entity Conversions (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - HB 1831 (03) Dogs Injuring or Killing Other Companion Animals (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - HB 1832 (03) Code Adam Alerts; Virginia Amber Alert Program (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - HB 1833 (03) Information to be Provided Prior to Abortion; Adoption (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - HB 1834 (03) Scoliosis Screening for Public School Students (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - HB 1836 (03) Recording Certificate of Satisfaction (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - HB 1838 (03) Taxpayer's Budget Bill of Rights (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - HB 1840 (03) Lost Evidences of Debt (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - HB 1842 (03) Retention of District Court Records (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - HB 1844 (03) Secretary of Health and Human Resources; Adoption Awareness Campaign (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - HB 1845 (03) Electronic Filing of Court Documents (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - HB 1851 (03) Development of Former Federal Areas (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - HB 1854 (03) Absentee Ballot Procedures (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - HB 1856 (03) Definition of a Firearm (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - HB 1857 (03) Removal of Illegal Signs from Highway Rights-of-Way (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - HB 1860 (03) Automated External Defibrillators; Public-Access Defibrillation (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - HB 1861 (03) Dangerous or Vicious Dogs (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - HB 1862 (03) Campaign Finance Disclosure Act; Forms/Filings/Reporting Requirements (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - HB 1863 (03) Professional Services; Independent Contractors (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - HB 1864 (03) Medical Malpractice; Independent Contractors (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - HB 1865 (03) Abandoning or Dumping Companion Animals (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - HB 1866 (03) Possession and Ownership of Companion Animals (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - HB 1868 (03) Senior Citizens Higher Education Act; Emergency (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - HB 1869 (03) Medicaid; Prohibited Acts (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - HB 1870 (03) Transfer/Copies of Patient Records Upon Sale/Relocation of Practice (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - HB 1871 (03) Health Professions; Multistate Nursing Compact (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - HB 1872 (03) Budget Bill; Additional Funds in the Revenue Stabilization Fund (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - HB 1874 (03) Voluntary Contributions by Hunters (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - HB 1875 (03) Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Board (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - HB 1876 (03) Water and Sewer Charges (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - HB 1877 (03) Workers' Compensation; Infectious Disease Presumption (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - HB 1881 (03) Service Districts (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - HB 1884 (03) Rural Rustic Road Program (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - HB 1885 (03) Local Government Health Insurance Programs; Volunteer Fire and Rescue (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - HB 1886 (03) Health Insurance; Coverage for Reconstructive Breast Surgery (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - HB 1888 (03) Civil Penalties for Zoning Violations (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - HB 1889 (03) Virginia Petroleum Products Franchise Act (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - HB 1896 (03) School Board Employees; Compensation Schedule (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - HB 1899 (03) Schools of Optometry; Enrollment Funding (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - HB 1900 (03) Health Professions; Practice of Dentistry (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - HB 1902 (03) All-Terrain Vehicles (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - HB 1903 (03) Oversize and Overweight Vehicles (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - HB 1904 (03) Overweight Permits for Certain Trucks (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - HB 1905 (03) Bail Bondsmen (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - HB 1906 (03) Medical Malpractice; Expert Witnesses (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - HB 1907 (03) Student Expulsions; Possession of Air Rifle or BB Gun (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - HB 1911 (03) Traffic Infractions; Penalty (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - HB 1913 (03) Individual Income Tax; Refund Checkoff for Historic Resources Fund (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - HB 1914 (03) Income Tax; Foreign Source Income (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - HB 1915 (03) Jurisdiction of Juvenile Court; When Divested (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - HB 1916 (03) Use of Accrued Annual Leave for Military Service (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - HB 1917 (03) State Grievance Procedure (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - HB 1918 (03) Certificate of Forensic Scientist as Evidence (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - HB 1919 (03) Failure to File Inventory (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - HB 1920 (03) Commissioners of Accounts (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - HB 1921 (03) Fiduciary Duties; Probate Tax (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - HB 1922 (03) Writs of Actual Innocence (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - HB 1923 (03) Death Penalty; Mental Retardation (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - HB 1924 (03) Notice of Release on Parole (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - HB 1925 (03) Technology Infrastructure Projects Added to Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act of 2002 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - HB 1926 (03) Information Technology Investment Board; Virginia Information Technologies Agency; Chief Information Officer (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - HB 1927 (03) Procurement of Information Technology; Reverse Auctioning (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - HB 1928 (03) Crimes; Money Laundering (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - HB 1929 (03) Unemployment Compensation; Weekly Benefit Amount (Box 76, Folder 3)